RG 029, Military Census
Connecticut State Library
Military Census Bureau records
1917-1920
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Military Census Bureau
214 cubic feet
Includes correspondence, administrative papers, schedules, questionnaires, punched cards, tabulations, summaries, related materials on Conn. residents, industry, agriculture, and files of Charles A. Goodwin, head of the military census bureau, and Frank D. Cheney, director of the industrial survey.
RG029
Multiple
Historical Note
In February 1917 the Connecticut General Assembly directed Governor Marcus H. Holcomb "to procure certain information relative to the resources of the State," especially about "men and materials available for use in the event of war."
Scope and Content
Approximately 502,980 sheets of the manpower census were completed and arranged in numerical order. An index card was prepared for each sheet and arranged under each town alphabetically by surname. Each card gives the name, address, and form number. Known as the Military Census, the most significant part was a manpower census of all male inhabitants over the age of sixteen taken in 1917-1918. However, additional surveys included such things as farms, crops, livestock, automobiles, doctors, nurses, and factories.
Related Material
RG 030, Council of Defense.
Index Terms
Persons:
Cheney, Frank D; Goodwin, Charles A
Subjects:
Agriculture -- Connecticut; Aliens; Connecticut -- Census; Industrial surveys; World War, 1914-1918 -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Card indexes; Correspondence; Lists (document genres); Questionnaires; Reports; Scrapbooks
Restrictions on Access
Some of these records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Alternative Form Available
In 1988 and 1989 the Genealogical Society of Utah microfilmed the completed forms and index cards and provided the State Library with a donor copy of each series. The index cards are on 16mm microfilm arranged by town and then alphabetically by surname. If a card for a name is located, researchers should take down the form number(s). The forms are arranged numerically on 35mm microfilm. Researchers should consult Series 2 of this finding aid to find the microfilm roll that includes the form in question. Form numbers appear in the upper right hand corner of each sheet. Since numbers on many of the original forms are faded, researchers may have difficulty in reading them, but the sheets are in numerical order on the microfilm.
The State Archives is treating the microfilm as the use copy. Hence, access to the original sheets are subject to the. The History and Genealogy staff does not search or provide copies from microfilmed records, and the State Library's copies of these films are not available on inter-library loan. However, a list of who can make copies for a fee is available and films may be used at.
Container List
- Series 1. Census Returns, 1917-1920; all except number 22, T000580; number 22, T003191
  - 1. Military census scrapbook, 1917-1918; 3 inches (Box Item 1)
    Mounted copies of forms, documents, newspaper clippings, and letters pertaining to the establishment of the Military Census and related surveys. There is a table of contents in the front.
  - 2. File of Charles A. Goodwin, 1917; 5 inches (Box 1)
    Goodwin was head of the Military Census Bureau.
    Administrative materials, including copies of documents on the British Registration Act of 1915 and three notebooks containing summaries of the manpower census results.
  - 3. Administrative and reference papers, 1917-1918; 5 inches (Box 2)
    State Library correspondence concerning the census, with copies of forms used, sample tables, instructions, summary reports and related materials.
    Correspondence is alphabetical. Other materials unarranged.
  - 4. Form requests, 1917; 10 inches
    Requests for forms by firms.
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - A-Q (Box 3)
    - R-Z (Box 4)
  - 5. Correspondence, 1917-1918; 15 inches
    Incoming and copies of outgoing correspondence.
    Arranged alphabetically by town.
    - Andover-Killingly (Box 5)
    - Killingworth-Portland (Box 6)
    - Preston-Woodstock (Box 5)
  - Records pertaining to Military Census compilations
    - 6. Summaries, tabulations and schedules, 1917-1918; 2 feet (Box 8 and Items 2-12 (oversize))
      Tables and lists of data collected in the Manpower Census, the Automobile Census and the Nurses' Census. Totals and names of registrants are shown by class (or "Group"), county, town, age group and occupation. Classes are follows: Class I, Citizens without dependents; Class II, Citizens with dependents; Class III, Physically unfit; Class IV, Holders of first papers for citizenship; Class V, Friendly aliens; Class VI, Enemy aliens. An itemized list of the files is at the beginning.
      There is no item 8.
    - 7. Tabulations and miscellaneous summaries, 4 inches (Box 9 and Item 13 oversize)
    - 8. List of occupations, 5 inches (Box 10)
      Fairfild and Litchfield farmes (photostat lists), wireless operators, with and without dependents (photostat), physicians (photostats and originals), nurses in Connecticut as of June 1918 (original and photostat), photographers (originals).
    - 9. Lists of Fairfield County male residents age 16-20 without dependents, 1917; 3 inches (Box 11)
      This is a list as prepared by the Bureau and sent to the towns for draft registration use.
      Alphabetical by town.
    - 10. Lists of Hartland men who registered in June 1917 and September 1918, .5 inches (Box 11)
    - 11. Records of the personal census, 1917; 4 inches (Box 12)
      Complete census of Waterbury (photostat and original), partial census of Greenwich (orignal), list of citizens refusing to answer the census agent (photostat), list of those men of Fairfield County that are eligible for military service, i.e., are 19 or 20 years old by June 1918 (original), male residents of Barkhamsted, age included (photostat), summary of draft age resources Hartford and Litchfield County (photostat), Bloomfield men age 21-30 from school register (original), Coventry men, age included (photostat), North Haven men, age included, non-residents with no information.
    - 12. Compilations of men physically fit, circa 1917; 5 feet
      Men, age 21-30. Some photostats and some orignal copies.
      Boxes 13-22 arranged alphabetically by town. Boxes 23-24 arranged alphbetically by county.
      - Andover-Bridgeport (Box 13)
      - Bridgeport-Danbury (Box 14)
      - Darien-Hampton (Box 15)
      - Hartford (Box 16)
      - Hartland-Milford (Box 17)
      - Monroe-New Haven (Box 18)
      - New Haven-Oxford (Box 19)
      - Plainfield-Suffield (Box 20)
      - Thomaston-Waterbury (Box 21)
      - Waterbury-Woodstock (Box 22)
      - Hartford, Litchfield, Middlesex Counties (Box 23)
      - New Haven, New London, Tolland, Windham Counties (Box 24)
    - 13. List of indivuduals who participated in taking the Waterbury census, 1917; 1 inch (Box 24)
      Incomplete, some pages missing.
    - 14. Lists of New Haven residents who are citizens, circa 1917; 1 foot (Box 25)
      Arranged alphabetically by occupation.
    - 15. Military census questionnaires, 1917; 155 boxes
      RESTRICTED. The microfilm listed in Series 2 is the use copy of these records.
      Individual form reports filled ou by or for male inhabitants of Connecticut, giving information on personal history, training, experience, etc.
      Arranged numerically. Indexed by item 16 below.
    - 16. Index to questionnaires, 1917
      RESTRICTED.
      Card index to item 15 above, giving name, address and questionnaire number.
      Arranged alphabetically by town, thereunder by name.
    - 17. Military census data punched cards, 1917
      Punched cards carrying name, street and coded data from the questionnaires in item 15.
      Arranged in various groups, by occupation, age, nationality, etc.
      The code has not been found and the cards could not be tabulated without repunching them.
    - 18. Card record of volunteer census takers, 1917
      Arranged by town.
      - Andover-Roxbury (Box 25a)
      - Salem-Woodstock; Cards not matched with towns (Box 25b)
    - 18a. Card file of census information retained by towns, 1917 (Box 25b)
  - Lists of Aliens
    - 19. Lists of enemy aliens, circa 1917
      - German-Austrians
        Two photostat copies and one partially complete orignial list.
        Arranged by county number.
        - 1. Hartford; 2. New Haven; 3. New London; 4. Fairfield (Box 26)
        - 5. Windham; 6. Middlesesx; 7. Litchfield; 8. Tolland (Box 27)
      - Italians
        Photostat copy only.
        - 1. Hartford; 2. New Haven (Box 28)
        - 3. New London; 4. Fairfield; 5. Windham; 6. Middlesesx; 7. Litchfield; 8. Tolland (Box 29)
    - 20. Lists of aliens
      Compilations of aliens residing in the state.
      Arranged alphabetically by nationality.
      - Canadiens, Danes, English (Box 30)
      - German, Irish, Indian, Welsh, Poles (Box 31)
      - Poles, Russians (Box 32)
      - Russains, Scotch, Swedes (Box 33)
    - 21. Miscellaneous materials pertaining to aliens (Box 34)
  - Records pertaining to the Agricultural Survey
    - 22. Index to farm owners or operators, 1918; T003191
      Card index or list containing name and address, with one or two reference numbers (questionnaire number and town code).
      Alphabetical by name.
      - A-Bi (Box 1)
      - Bl-Ch (Box 2)
      - Cl-E (Box 3)
      - El-G (Box 4)
      - H-Je (Box 5)
      - Jo-Lo (Box 6)
      - Lu-Ne (Box 7)
      - Ni-Re (Box 8)
      - Ri-Sm (Box 9)
      - Sn-Wal (Box 10)
      - Wam-Z (Box 11)
    - 23. Agricultural Survey data punched cards, 1918
      Punched cards recording data from the Agricultural Survey questionnaires (See item 29 below).
      Arranged by county and thereunder grouped by subject - acreage, livestock, crops, etc.
    - 24. Lists of citizen farmers (Box 35)
      Citizen farmers with/without dependents; fit/unfit for service. Original and photostat copies.
    - 25. Agricultural Survey administrative papers, 1918 (Box 36)
      Forms, instructions, codes, reports, fragmentary series of questionnaires and related materials.
      Unarranged.
    - 26. Agricultural Survey summaries and lists, 1918 (Box Items 14-16 oversize)
      Summary tables by county, thereunder by product; by product, thereunder by county and town.
    - 27. Agricultural Survey correspondence, 1918-1920 (Box 37)
      Incoming correspondence and copies of outgoing letters to and from George Goddard.
      This series is divided into two parts. The first arrangement is alphabetical by county; the second is a general file arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
    - 28. Agricultural Survey lists, 1917-18919 (Box 38-40)
      Original lists compiled for the Connecticut Agricultural Survey. Included are lists of tobacco and corn growers, acreage studies, farm machinery and livestock. The entire state is not represented.
    - 29. Papers of the state-wide Agricultural Survey, 1918 (Box 41-59)
      Original questionnaires completed in compliance with the COnnecticut Council of Defense, agricultural survey. The survey includes questiones related to the land area, crops planted for 1917 and 1918, "probable area with adequate harvesting equipment," "machinery on hand" and "employees."
      The questionnaires are grouped roughly by county, apparently in the order in which they were received. A list is included in Box 41.
  - Records pertaining to the Industrial Census
    - 30. Industrial Census administrative correspondence, 1917 (Box 60)
      Alphabetical by correspondent.
    - 31. Correspondence of Frank D. Cheney, 1917-1919
      Cheney was Director of the Industrial Census.
      - Correspondence, 1917-1918
        Arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
        - A-C (Box 61)
        - E-W (Box 62)
      - Letterbooks
        Arranged chronologically.
        - 1917 June 19-1918 July 12, 1 volume (Box Item 17)
        - 1918 July 13-1919 January 27, 1 volume (Box Item 18)
    - 32. Industrial Census questionnaires, 1917 (Box 63)
      Form reports.
      Arranged alphabetical by name of company, followed by lists of committees, etc.
    - 33. Industrial Survey questionnaires, reports, 1918
      Arranged alphabetically by product.
      - Boats and Marine; Clothing; Contractors; Hospital; Leather; Metal (Box 64)
      - Metal (Box 65)
      - Paper; Silver; Textiles; Wood (Box 66)
    - 34. Survey of Industrial Corporations, 1917 (Box 67-68)
      Arranged numerically in the order in which they were received.
    - 35. Records of corporations not involved in government work, 1917 (Box 69)
      Photostat list of corporations involved in the production of "metal, wood, textiles, miscellaneous, and clothing."
    - 36. Miscellaneous lists of Connecticut corporations, 1917 (Box 69)
      Original lists.
    - 37. "Second White Industrial Survey", 1917 (Box 69)
      Form reports discarded by Frank D. Cheney "for no apparent reason."
    - 38. Automobile Census Bureau correspondence, 1917-1918 (Box 70)
      Incoming and copies of outgoing correspondence, with both firms and residents.
      Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent.
    - 39. Lists of individuals owning automobiles (Box 71)
  - Miscellaneous records pertaining to the Military Census
    - 40. Sample forms used in taking the military census. (Box 71)
    - 41. Clippings relating to the Military Census, 1917 (Box 71)
    - 42. Miscellaneous materials relating to the taking of the Military Census (Box 71)
    - 43. Unidentified list (Box 71)
    - 44. List of codes used by the Connecticut Military Census Bureau, 1917 (Box 72)
  - Records pertaining to the Census of Nursing
    - 45. Correspondence relating to completing census forms, 1917-1918 (Box 73)
    - 46. Correspondence relating to locating doctors and nurses who have not registerd, 1917
      Arranged alphabeticaly by town.
      - Andover-Meriden (Box 74)
      - Middlebury-Woodstock (Box 75)
    - Forms submitted by nurses, 1917 (Box 76-84)
      Microfilm copy available for use copy. See History and Genealogy staff.
      Arranged roughly by classification. Code to classification system is in Box 76.
    - 48. Assorted forms, lists, and applications, 1917-1918 (Box 85)
  - Records pertaining to the Industrial Census
    - 49. Card file of manufactureres, circa 1918 (Box Card drawers 15-16)
      Arranged by type of industry, then alphabetically by company name.
    - 50. Manufacturers active plants, circa 1918 (Box Card drawer 17)
      Arranged alphbetically by company name.
    - 51. Manufacturers reserve plants, circa 1918 (Box Card drawer 18)
      Arranged alphabetically by company name.
- Series 2. Microfilm, 1917-1918; 1988-089
  Arranged numerically by sheet number.
  Microfilm located in the History and Genealogy reading room.
  - 1-20, 23 exposures; 1533560 (Reel 1)
  - 1-889, 898 exposures; 1533560 (Reel 1)
  - 890-2660, 1790 exposures; 1533561 (Reel 2)
  - 2661-4470, 1826 exposures; 1533562 (Reel 3)
  - 4471-5299, 846 exposures; 1533563 (Reel 4)
  - 5300-6140, 857 exposures; 1533734 (Reel 5)
  - 6141-7899, 1778 exposures; 1533735 (Reel 6)
  - 7900-9679, 1806 exposures; 1533736 (Reel 7)
  - 9680-11519, 1770 exposures; 1533737 (Reel 8)
  - 11520-13239, 1751 exposures; 1533738 (Reel 9)
  - 13240-14799, 1689 exposures; 1533739 (Reel 10)
  - 14800-16439, 1574 exposures; 1491963 (Reel 11)
  - 16440-17499, 1075 exposures; 1533826 (Reel 12)
  - 17500-17999, 512 exposures; 1492207 (Reel 13)
  - 18000-19299, 1356 exposures; 1535271 (Reel 14)
  - 19300-20900, 1868 exposures; 1535272 (Reel 15)
  - 20901-22740, 1904 exposures; 1535273 (Reel 16)
  - 22741-24599, 1890 exposures; 1535427 (Reel 17)
  - 24600-26139, 1653 exposures; 1535428 (Reel 18)
  - 26140-27870, 1802 exposures; 1535429 (Reel 19)
  - 27871-29680, 1890 exposures; 1535430 (Reel 20)
  - 29681-31439, 1816 exposures; 1535431 (Reel 21)
  - 31440-33209, 1808 exposures; 1535432 (Reel 22)
  - 33210-34959, 1805 exposures; 1535433 (Reel 23)
  - 34960-36719, 1812 exposures; 1535434 (Reel 24)
  - 3672038280, 1898 exposures; 1535435 (Reel 25)
  - 38281-40049, 1813 exposures; 1535436 (Reel 26)
  - 40050-41810, 1888 exposures; 1535437 (Reel 27)
  - 41811-43139, 1484 exposures; 1535438 (Reel 28)
  - 43140-45059, 1954 exposures; 1535555 (Reel 29)
  - 45050-46940, 1939 exposures; 1535556 (Reel 30)
  - 46941-48859, 1960 exposures; 1535557 (Reel 31)
  - 48860-50739, 1910 exposures; 1535558 (Reel 32)
  - 50740-52699, 1982 exposures; 1535559 (Reel 33)
  - 52700-54609, 1950 exposures; 1535560 (Reel 34)
  - 54610-56260, 1696 exposures; 1535561 (Reel 35)
  - 56261-58169, 1969 exposures; 1535562 (Reel 36)
  - 58170-59779, 1857 exposures; 1535563 (Reel 37)
  - 59780-61070, 1937 exposures; 1535581 (Reel 38)
  - 61071-62349, 1602 exposures; 1535582 (Reel 39)
  - 62350-63649, 1864 exposures; 1535728 (Reel 40)
    Sheets 63000-63649 are missing.
  - 63800-65410, 1951 exposures; 1535729 (Reel 41)
  - 65411-67280, 1929 exposures; 1535730 (Reel 42)
  - 67281-69070, 1859 exposures; 1535731 (Reel 43)
  - 69071-70869, 1842 exposures; 1535732 (Reel 44)
  - 70870-72680, 1890 exposures; 1535733 (Reel 45)
  - 72681-74749, 1942 exposures; 1535734 (Reel 46)
    Sheets 73147-73326 and 73330-73341 are missing.
  - 74750-76559, 1865 exposures; 1535735 (Reel 47)
  - 76560-78380, 1865 exposures; 1535736 (Reel 48)
  - 78381-80190, 1861 exposures; 1535771 (Reel 49)
  - 80191-82060, 1896 exposures; 1535772 (Reel 50)
  - 82061-83549, 1623 exposures; 1535773 (Reel 51)
  - 83550-85059, 1649 exposures; 1535774 (Reel 52)
  - 85060-86860, 1879 exposures; 1535850 (Reel 53)
  - 86861-88650, 1862 exposures; 1535851 (Reel 54)
  - 88651-90290, 1742 exposures; 1535852 (Reel 55)
  - 90291-92120, 1868 exposures; 1535853 (Reel 56)
  - 92121-93959, 1870 exposures; 1535854 (Reel 57)
  - 93960-95769, 1874 exposures; 1535855 (Reel 58)
  - 95770-97590, 1877 exposures; 1535856 (Reel 59)
  - 97591-99450, 1916 exposures; 1535857 (Reel 60)
  - 99451-101269, 1872 exposures; 1535858 (Reel 61)
  - 101270-103090, 1873 exposures; 1535859 (Reel 62)
  - 103091-104620, 1636 exposures; 1535860 (Reel 63)
  - 104621-106419, 1876 exposures; 1535861 (Reel 64)
  - 106420-108219, 1881 exposures; 1536042 (Reel 65)
  - 108220-110279, 1866 exposures; 1536043 (Reel 66)
  - 110280-112049, 1885 exposures; 1536044 (Reel 67)
  - 112050-113459, 1892 exposures; 1536045 (Reel 68)
  - 113460-115259, 1886 exposures; 1536046 (Reel 69)
  - 115260-117099, 1899 exposures; 1536047 (Reel 70)
  - 117100-118899, 1886 exposures; 1536048 (Reel 71)
  - 117100-118899, 1886 exposures; 1536048 (Reel 72)
  - 118900-120719, 1905 exposures; 1536049 (Reel 72)
  - 120720-122520, 1882 exposures; 1536050 (Reel 73)
  - 122521-124040, 1639 exposures; 1536051 (Reel 74)
  - 124041-125839, 23 exposures; 1536052 (Reel 75)
  - 125840-127679, 1912 exposures; 1536053 (Reel 76)
  - 127680-129479, 1880 exposures; 1536054 (Reel 77)
  - 129480-131269, 1874 exposures; 1536055 (Reel 78)
  - 131270-133099, 1885 exposures; 1536056 (Reel 79)
  - 133100-134939, 1883 exposures; 1536057 (Reel 80)
  - 134940-136750, 1879 exposures; 1536058 (Reel 81)
  - 136751-138599, 1887 exposures; 1536150 (Reel 82)
  - 138600-140409, 1865 exposures; 1536151 (Reel 83)
  - 140410-142219, 1885 exposures; 1536152 (Reel 84)
  - 142220-144050, 1881 exposures; 1536153 (Reel 85)
  - 144051-145880, 1878 exposures; 1536154 (Reel 86)
  - 145881-147710, 1871 exposures; 1536155 (Reel 87)
  - 147711-149519, 1880 exposures; 1536156 (Reel 88)
  - 149520-151339, 1873 exposures; 1536157 (Reel 89)
  - 151340-153210, 1913 exposures; 1536158 (Reel 90)
  - 153211-155030, 1875 exposures; 1536159 (Reel 91)
  - 155031-156790, 1868 exposures; 1536160 (Reel 92)
  - 1536161, 1878 exposures; 156161 (Reel 93)
  - 158611-160409, 1863 exposures; 1536162 (Reel 94)
  - 160410-161939, 1640 exposures; 1536163 (Reel 95)
  - 161940-163770, 1870 exposures; 1536164 (Reel 96)
  - 163771-165609, 1882 exposures; 1536165 (Reel 97)
  - 165610-167399, 1866 exposures; 1536166 (Reel 98)
  - 167400-169240, 1879 exposures; 1536333 (Reel 99)
  - 169241-171049, 1874 exposures; 1536334 (Reel 100)
  - 171050-172859, 1879 exposures; 1536335 (Reel 101)
  - 172860-174670, 1866 exposures; 1536336 (Reel 102)
  - 174671-176469, 1875 exposures; 1536337 (Reel 103)
  - 176470-177890, 1579 exposures; 1536338 (Reel 104)
  - 177891-179679, 1866 exposures; 1536339 (Reel 105)
  - 179680-181470, 1863 exposures; 1536340 (Reel 106)
  - 181471-183224, 1908 exposures; 1536341 (Reel 107)
  - 183200-184999, 1901 exposures; 1536342 (Reel 108)
  - 185000-186749, 1837 exposures; 1547439 (Reel 109)
  - 186750-188569, 1877 exposures; 1547440 (Reel 110)
  - 188570-190419, 1927 exposures; 1547441 (Reel 111)
  - 190420-192229, 1878 exposures; 1547442 (Reel 112)
  - 192230-194039, 1867 exposures; 1547443 (Reel 113)
  - 194040-195849, 1876 exposures; 1547444 (Reel 114)
  - 195850-197610, 1867 exposures; 1547445 (Reel 115)
  - 197611-199410, 1870 exposures; 1547446 (Reel 116)
  - 199411-201099, 1861 exposures; 1547447 (Reel 117)
  - 201100-202879, 1969 exposures; 1547486 (Reel 118)
  - 202880-204399, 1630 exposures; 1547487 (Reel 119)
  - 204400-205539, 1185 exposures; 1547488 (Reel 120)
  - 205540-207340, 1864 exposures; 1547489 (Reel 121)
  - 207341-209109, 1865 exposures; 1547490 (Reel 122)
  - 209110-210900, 1861 exposures; 1547558 (Reel 123)
  - 210901-212729, 1872 exposures; 1547559 (Reel 124)
  - 212730-214519, 1853 exposures; 1547560 (Reel 125)
  - 214520-216319, 1969 exposures; 1547561 (Reel 126)
  - 216320-218130, 1869 exposures; 1547562 (Reel 127)
  - 218131-219959, 1874 exposures; 1547563 (Reel 128)
  - 219960-221760, 1857 exposures; 1547564 (Reel 129)
  - 221761-223579, 1867 exposures; 1547565 (Reel 130)
  - 223580-225360, 1860 exposures; 1547566 (Reel 131)
  - 225361-227149, 1850 exposures; 1547567 (Reel 132)
  - 227150-228330, 1227 exposures; 1547703 (Reel 133)
  - 228331-230099, 1843 exposures; 1547704 (Reel 134)
  - 230100-231860, 1841 exposures; 1547705 (Reel 135)
  - 231861-233519, 1795 exposures; 1547706 (Reel 136)
  - 233520-235239, 1808 exposures; 1547707 (Reel 137)
  - 235240-237009, 1832 exposures; 1547708 (Reel 138)
  - 2327010-238819, 1863 exposures; 1547709 (Reel 139)
  - 238820-240550, 1808 exposures; 1547710 (Reel 140)
  - 240551-242300, 1828 exposures; 1547711 (Reel 141)
  - 242301-244029, 1843 exposures; 1547712 (Reel 142)
  - 244030-245470, 1553 exposures; 1547713 (Reel 143)
  - 245471-247279, 1861 exposures; 1547714 (Reel 144)
  - 247280-249019, 1805 exposures; 1547715 (Reel 145)
  - 249020-250829, 1864 exposures; 1547752 (Reel 146)
  - 250830-252570, 1846 exposures; 1547753 (Reel 147)
  - 252571-254289, 1779 exposures; 1547754 (Reel 148)
  - 254290-255999, 1812 exposures; 1547755 (Reel 149)
  - 256000-257469, 1571 exposures; 1547756 (Reel 150)
  - 257470-259219, 1815 exposures; 1547964 (Reel 151)
  - 259220-260959, 1811 exposures; 1547965 (Reel 152)
  - 260960-262659, 1804 exposures; 1547966 (Reel 153)
  - 262660-264359, 1806 exposures; 1547967 (Reel 154)
  - 264360-266110, 1829 exposures; 1547968 (Reel 155)
    Sheets 266051-266099 are missing.
  - 266111-268009, 1821 exposures; 1547969 (Reel 156)
    Sheets 266823-266999 are missing.
  - 268010-269579, 1680 exposures; 1547970 (Reel 157)
  - 269580-271369, 1864 exposures; 1547971 (Reel 158)
  - 271370-272839, 1592 exposures; 1547972 (Reel 159)
  - 272840-274639, 1863 exposures; 1547973 (Reel 160)
  - 274640-276310, 1815 exposures; 1547974 (Reel 161)
  - 276311-278079, 1854 exposures; 1548190 (Reel 162)
  - 278080-279859, 1854 exposures; 1548191 (Reel 163)
  - 279860-281570, 1806 exposures; 1548192 (Reel 164)
  - 281571-283280, 1784 exposures; 1548193 (Reel 165)
  - 283281-284979, 1820 exposures; 1548194 (Reel 166)
    Final exposures fogged?